It can't be.
محال
No... No...
...مستحيل... مستحيل
Pedro-san sacrificed himself...
...بيدرو-سان قد ضحى بحياته
If only we were... if only we were...!
...لو أننا كنا أكثر... أكثر
If only we were stronger...
...أكثر قوة
Our enemies are the ones who should be crying.
دعوا البكاء لأعدائنا
We cannot allow ourselves to be upset.
يجب ألّا نفقد رباطة جأشنا
Hey, Jinbe-san !
مهلًا يا جينبي-سان
How could you say something so cruel?!
كيف تخبرنا بهذا بكل برود؟
Just because you spent the least amount of time with Pedro doesn't mean that–
...فأنت لم تعرف بيدرو-سان بقدرنا
I'm just saying that we shouldn't let our guards down!
أنا أطلب منكم ألّا تفقدوا تركيزكم
We had our backs against the wall on that coastline...
كنا في وضعٍ حرج عند الساحل
Pedro knew that we were in a dangerous situation and was prepared to sacrifice himself whenever necessary.
قرر التضحية بنفسه لأنّه أدرك مدى خطورة الوضع
This is...
...هذا
Pedro's victory!
نصر بيدرو
This is an unprecedented series of events for them!
إنّها خسارات ذريعة وغير مسبوقة بالنسبة لهم
Your strength really drove Big Mom into a corner!
قوتكم دفعت بيغ مام إلى الهاوية
"Keep going!"
امضوا قدمًا»؟»
Luffy understood the stakes instantly...
...شعر لوفي بذلك فورًا
and decided to take the enemy on all by himself.
وقرر مواجهة العدو وحده
Katakuri has a bounty of over one billion! It's an all or nothing situation.
مكافأة كاتاكوري تفوق المليار إنّها مواجهة بعنوان أكون أو لا أكون
We are still in Totto Land!
ما زلنا في الإقليم البحري لتوتولاند
Sooner or later, the pirate queen of this country, Big Mom, will be on our tail!
لذا ستطاردنا ملكة قراصنة هذه البلاد بيغ مام قريبًا
And her fleet could close in on us from all directions at any time!
وقد يُحيط بنا أسطولها من جميع الاتجاهات في أي لحظة
So until we escape from Big Mom's territory...
...لذا ريثما تخرجون من منطقة بيغ مام
we must not let down our guard! Don't you hear Pedro saying that?!
حريّ بكم ألّا تفقدوا تركيزكم أليس هذا ما يقوله بيدرو داخلكم؟
I'm very sorry.
أقدّم خالص اعتذاري
I was way out of line.
فأنا لم أتمالك نفسي
Nami, give us directions!
نامي، زودينا بالتعليمات
Okay!
أجل
Sanji-kun and the others will be sailing to us from Cacao Island,
سيأتينا سانجي-كن والآخرون من جزيرة الكاكاو
so we need to make sure we don't miss them.
لذا لا نريد أن نفوّت مقابلتهم
There's a strong wind coming! It's a tailwind!
ستهب رياح قوية قريبًا، وهي رياح خلفية
So, steer to starboard!
لذا توجه نحو الميمنة
Hard a-starboard!
أقصى الميمنة
We'll catch the wind on the starboard side and head straight west!
لنستغل الرياح في جانب الميمنة ونتجه للغرب مباشرة
We'll take a direct route!
سنسلك الطريق الأقصر
Roger!
عُلم
I'll go refill the cola we used!
سأعيد تعبئة الكولا التي استعملناها للتو
I'll watch for enemies!
سأتولى المراقبة
Okay!
حسنًا
I'm in position!
أنا في مركزي
Uh-huh!
أجل
I'll help you monitor the sea currents!
دعوا لي مراقبة التيارات
They're coming from six o'clock!
إنّهم قادمون باتجاه الساعة السادسة
There's a person?!
شخص؟
I-It can't be!
مـ-محال
Cake!
كعكة
It can't be... that can't... that can't be possible!
محال، هذا... هذا غير معقول
Big Mom is walking on the water!
بيغ مام تسير على الماء
No way! That's ridiculous!
محال، كيف يُعقل ذلك؟
It's not water... It's...
...تلك ليست مياه، بل
candy?!
حلوى؟
She's walking on a large blob of moving candy!
إنّها تسير على كتلة ضخمة من الحلوى المتحركة
Using candy?!
تستخدم الحلوى؟
Hey, does that mean...?
...مهلًا، أيعني ذلك
The only person capable of producing that...
...الشخص الوحيد القادر على صنعها
It must be... him !
لا بدّ أنّه الفاعل
Lick...
بيرورين
Candy Sea Slug!
حلوى محار البحر
Where did Zeus go?
أين ذهب زيوس؟
It's his job to help Mama cross the sea!
من واجبه حمل ماما عبر البحر
It can't be...
محال
But I suppose that's fine... because I have a score to settle with them!
على كلٍّ، لدي دافع قوي الآن للنيل منهم
Pedro sacrificed his own life!
بيدرو ضحّى بحياته من أجل التخلّص منه
I'll remember... that jaguar mink's face!
سأتذكر وجه فهد المينك البغيض ذاك
Isn't that right, Napoleon? There's nothing more humiliating!
ألستُ محقًّا يا نابليون؟ لا شيء أكثر إذلالًا من ذلك
It is a grievous crime in this land.
طاقم قبعة القش تعدوا حدود الإجرام في أرضنا
The Straw Hats have no future here.
لا مستقبل لهم بعد الآن
How should I torment...
...إذًا كيف
his companions to sate my rage?!
أعذّبُ رفاقه حتّى أشعر بالرضا؟
Everyone's gone!
أين رحل الجميع؟
I really wanna eat some flames! I'm losing my strength...
...أود تناول النيران بسرعة، إني أفقد قواي
I wanna eat thunderclouds, too...
...أنا أيضًا أود تناول السحب الرعدية
Oh... So Lola-chan, who we met at Thriller Bark, was a master at making chocolate?!
ماذا؟ إذًا كانت لولا-تشان من ثريلر بارك خبيرة في إعداد الشوكولاتة؟
That's right. Lola was the minister of chocolate on Cacao Island,
أجل، كانت لولا وزيرة الشوكولاتة في جزيرة الكاكاو
but after she left, the position was never filled!
لكن ذلك المنصب بقي شاغرًا منذ مغادرتها
Oh, how come?
ما السبب إذًا؟
Because the presumed candidate here keeps rejecting the position.
لأنّ المرشحة الأبرز بين الجميع هنا رفضت العرض
Isn't that right, Pudding?
أليس كذلك يا بودينغ؟
B-Because, to me...
...ذ-ذلك لأنني
the only minister of chocolate for Chocolat Town should be Sister Lola!
أعتبر أختي الكبيرة لولا هي وزيرة الشوكولاتة الوحيدة لبلدة الشوكولاتة
And I've always hoped that she would return someday...
وأتمنى أن تعود يومًا ما
I know how you feel, but...
...أتفهم شعوركِ، لكن
Could I be mistaken?
أأنا مخطئ؟
No...
...كلا
I-I think that's my daughter!
أ-أظن أنّها ابنتي
Hey! Hey!
أنتِ، أنتِ
Hey!
أنتِ
She's gone now...
لقد رحلت
Chiffon...
...شيفون
Hey! Come out from under there, Pudding!
بحقكِ، أخرجي من عندكِ يا بودينغ
N-No way!
كـ-كفاكِ مزاحًا
I'm wearing a wedding dress right now!
إنني أرتدي فستان الزفاف حاليًّا
If I sit on the carpet with that man,
لذا إن جلستُ على السجادة بجوار هذا الرجل
people will think that we just got married to each other!
فسيظنون أننا عروسين جديدين أقاما حفل زفافهما للتو
What people?
من هم؟
You never know who's watching! And I'll be annoyed if they think it!
لا تعرفين من قد يرانا، ويزعجني إن ظنّوا ذلك
It.. It'll... It'll really annoy me, okay?!
هذا... هـ-هذا يزعجني، أفهمتِ؟
Sorry about the trouble. Just don't fall, okay?
يؤسفني ذلك، لكن لا تسقطي
Sh-Shut up!
ا-اخرس
Oh! What a sweet man! He's worried about me!
يا له من طيّب، إنّه قلقٌ عليّ
Who do you think you are?! Whether I fall or not isn't your business!
بحقك، من تظن نفسك؟ سقوطي من عدمه ليس من شأنك
There's Cacao Island!
بوسعي رؤية جزيرة الكاكاو
All right! Let's start making the cake as soon as we arrive!
عظيم، لنبدأ بإعداد الكعكة فور وصولنا
Hey! Did you hear what I said, Sanji...
...انتظر، هل سمعت ما قلته يا سانجي
-san ?!
سان؟-
What an idiot!
يا له من أحمق
I can't believe he broke the mirror himself!
لقد حطّم المرآة بنفسه
Are you trying to sacrifice yourself to let your friends escape?!
أتحاول التضحية بنفسك ليتسنّى لرفاقك الهرب؟
I'm gonna kick your ass!
سوف أُبرحك ضربًا
Don't be ridiculous!
كفاك هراءً
Who do you think you're talking to?!
من تخاطب برأيك؟
Commander Katakuri has a bounty of one billion, fifty-seven million belly!
تبلغ مكافأة كاتاكوري-ساما مليار و57 مليون بيري
He's the strongest of the Three Sweet Commanders!
إنّه أقوى قادة الحلوى الثلاث
Hawk Gatling!
رشاش الصقر
I'm following your lead on this...
إنني أجاريك في تحركاتك
Am I doing it wrong?
هل أنفذها بشكل خاطئ؟
But... it's more efficient this way!
لكنها أكثر فاعلية بهذه الطريقة
That's Commander Katakuri for you!
كما هو متوقع من كاتاكوري-ساما
Commander Katakuri, that's so brutal!
ذلك قاسٍ يا كاتاكوري-ساما
I suppose you understand now.
أظن أنّك أدركت الآن
As I already told you... in terms of ability...
...كما أخبرتك سابقًا، من حيث القدرة
there's nothing you can do that I cannot.
ليس هنالك شيء يمكنك القيام به ولا يمكنني فعله
I have you beat in both speed and strength.
أنت أدنى مستوى منّي في السرعة والقوة
Rubber won't lose to mochi !
لن يخسر المطاط أمام كعكة موتشي
I'm not gonna lose!
أنا لن أخسر
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Hawk Stamp!
ختم الصقر
Is that it?
أهذا كلّ شيء؟
No way!
ليس بعد
He disappeared again!
اختفى مجدّدًا
I knew Commander Katakuri was in a different league!
كما توقعت، إنّ كاتاكوري-ساما في مستوى مختلف عنه
So you're trying strength next?
إذًا محاولتك التالية هي القوة؟
Give up already.
استسلم فحسب
What a huge punch!
يا لها من قبضة ضخمة
Gum-Gum...
غومو غومو نو
Elephant...
بندقية
Gun!
الفيل
Commander Katakuri's is even bigger!
قبضة كاتاكوري-ساما أضخم منها
Is that how you do...
هل نفذتُ ضربة «بندقية الفيل» بالشكل الصحيح؟
She's so beautiful in her wedding dress!
يا لجمالها وهي ترتدي فستان زفافها
I feel bad for her. Her wedding was ruined.
يا لها من مسكينة، لقد أُفسد حفل زفافها
But even with that sad look, she's still so beautiful!
رغم ملامحها الحزينة إلّا أنّها ما زالت جميلة
Oh! It's the minister of puffs!
وزيرة المعجنات
M-Madam Chiffon!
شـ-شيفون-ساما
Everyone, don't worry! Sister Chiffon is not the primary culprit of the revolt!
اطمئنوا جميعًا، أختي شيفون لا علاقة لها في التمرد
The one at fault is her husband: Gang Bege!
الخطأ يقع على عاتق زوجها غانغ بيجي
I'm sorry, Sister.
المعذرة
I told them that I'd threaten you and force you to help me make the cake.
أخبرتهم أنني سأهددكِ وأرغمكِ على مساعدتي في إعداد الكعكة
That's okay, Pudding. That's the position I'm in now.
لا عليك يا بودينغ، هذا ما أنا عليه حاليًّا في نظر العامة
Who could've expected such a happy wedding
لا أحد توقع أنّ الزفاف السعيد سيفسده اقتحام قبعة القش لوفي وخيانة بيجي
That Sanji man ruined it, too!
وكذلك كان سانجي محتالًا للغاية
What's done is done.
لا حيلة لمنع ما حدث
Madam Pudding, I'm sure you're having a hard time!
بودينغ-ساما، لا بدّ أنّكِ تمرين بوقتٍ عصيب
Mama must be angry.
أتساءل ما مدى غضب ماما؟
Yes, she's mad and hungry.
أجل، إنّها غاضبة وجائعة
In addition, she's on a ravenous rampage and may very well destroy this country.
الأدهى من ذلك، إنّها تمر بنوبة جوع وقد تدمر الدولة
Oh, how horrible...
...يا له من أمر مرعب
Is everything ready?
أكل شيء جاهز؟
Yes! About an hour ago, the 31 most renowned chefs from Whole Cake Island arrived here.
أجل، منذ ساعة تقريبًا جاء 31 طاهٍ من جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
We've been expecting you, Madam Pudding!
كنا بانتظارك يا بودينغ-ساما
We're the 31 head chefs of Whole Cake Island!
نحن نخبة الطُهاة في جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة وعددنا 31
We're the WCI 31!
اختصارٌ لجزيرة الكعكة الكاملة WCI
Sister Chiffon and I will make the wedding cake that can stop Mama.
سنتولى أنا وأختي شيفون إعداد كعكة الزفاف التي ستوقف هيجان ماما
Please help us.
أرجو أن تمدوا لنا يد العون
Yes, ma'am! We've already made preparations!
حاضر، لقد بدأنا مسبقًا في التحضيرات
Madam Pudding was the bride, so she was affected the most by what happened...
كانت العروس بودينغ-ساما المتضرر الأكبر مما حدث
You can count on me! I'm not gonna let Mama destroy our country!
اعتمدوا عليّ، لن أدع ماما تدمّر الدولة
Madam Pudding!
بودينغ-ساما
I can't believe she's overcoming the pain and overseeing the cake-making herself!
لا أصدّق أنّها تجاوزت ألمها وقررت الإشراف على إعداد الكعكة بنفسها
She's literally a goddess of salvation!
إنّها منقذتنا فعلًا
Good luck!
ابذلي جهدكِ
Go ahead and go inside with Rabiyan.
اسبقيني للداخل برفقة رابيان يا أختي
Okay.
أجل
Please, everyone! Listen to me!
أرجو أن تصغوا إليّ جميعًا
I need you to do me a favor!
أريد أن تسدوني معروفًا بسيطًا
We're going to risk our lives and bake the cake that will determine the fate of our country!
سنخاطر بأرواحنا ونعد الكعكة التي ستغير مصير دولتنا
We really need to concentrate!
نحن بأمسّ الحاجة إلى التركيز
So, please don't look inside the factory under any circumstance while we're at it!
لذا لا تنظروا أبدًا إلى داخل المصنع أثناء تواجدنا فيه
Yes, ma'am!
حاضر
And no matter who it is, don't let anyone look inside!
وأيضًا، لا تسمحوا لأيّ شخص بالنظر إلى الداخل كائنًا من كان
We understand, Madam Pudding!
مفهوم يا بودينغ-ساما
Thank you, everyone!
شكرًا لكم جميعًا
Good luck, Madam Pudding!
ابذلي جهدكِ يا بودينغ-ساما
This way, they won't see Sanji-san...
لن يكتشفوا أمر سانجي-سان بهذا الحال
And now, I've got to deal with the ones who will be helping us.
تبقى تولّي أمر العاملين معنا
Head Chefs! Come inside one at a time!
رؤساء الطهاة، ادخلوا واحدًا تلو الآخر
Head chef of the First Kitchen, Buche, reporting for duty.
رئيس طهاة المطبخ الأول بوش يتقدم للدخول
Stay still.
لا تتحرك
I'm gonna modify your memories...
سأعدّل ذكرياتك
Edit!
تعديل
Hey, let me down.
أنزلني
Okay!
حاضر
Here you go!
ها أنت ذا
That must've been a tough ride.
أحسنت صنعًا
We don't have much time,
الوقت يُداهمنا، لذا رسمتُ مخطط لكعكة الزفاف في الطريق
What?! You memorized it?
ماذا؟ هل تتذكرها؟
Pretty much.
بكل دقة
No way! It's easy to remember the shape, but how could you know the ingredients without tasting it?!
محال، ربما تتذكر شكلها لكن كيف عرفت مكوناتها من دون تذوقها حتّى؟
By smelling it.
من الرائحة
Seriously?!
بجدية؟
Now, hurry up! Every minute counts!
والآن دعونا نُسرع، فكل دقيقة ذات أهمية بالغة
Pudding-chan's chef outfit is so cute!
بودينغ-تشان تبدو فاتنة حتّى في رداء الطهاة
Madam Pudding, are you all right?!
بودينغ-ساما، أأنتِ بخير؟
Let's do it, Sir Husband!
لنبذل جهدنا يا سيدي المتزوج
Huh? Me?
ماذا؟ أنا؟
Come here!
تعال
I took out their memories of the incident earlier...
عدلتُ على ذكريات الطهاة عن الحادثة
In other words, they think the wedding finished without a hitch, and...
أي أنّهم يظنون أنّ الزفاف جرى كما ينبغي
that w... we are... m... married!
و-ونحن... مـ-متزوجان
But...
...ولكن
they think the wedding cake was ruined by unexpected weather
لقد أُفسدت كعكة الزفاف بسبب هطول أمطار غير متوقعة
and that Mama was enraged, so the cake has to be remade quickly.
مما أثار غضب ماما، لذا علينا الإسراع لإعداد الكعكة مجدّدًا
That is what they believe now.
هذا ما أعدتُ كتابته في ذكرياتهم
I see.
فهمت
Their memories of making the cake are still fresh, so they'll be useful to us!
ما تزال ذكرياتهم عن إعداد الكعكة الأولى سليمة مما سيساعدنا في إعدادها مجدّدًا
Who drew this blueprint and recipe for the wedding cake?!
من عمل هذا المخطط ووصفة كعكة الزفاف؟
Me!
أنا
Sir Husband, you drew this?!
سيدي المتزوج، أأنت من كتبها؟
Yeah. Let me know if there are any mistakes.
أجل، أخبروني إن وجدتم أي أخطاء
It's perfect!
إنّها مثالية
You even identified the hidden flavors
حتّى أنّك اكتشفت المكونات السرية التي استغرق رئيس الطهاة سترويزن أسبوعًا لإعدادها
I heard rumors you were skilled, but wow, you're amazing!
رغم أنني سمعتُ أنّك ماهر، إلّا أنّك فقت توقعاتي
And by an odd coincidence, as husband and wife...
...وبصفتكما زوجان، فإنّ إعداد هذه الكعكة سوف
Husband and wife?!
زوجان؟
..this cake will be your first project, strangely enough.
يكون تعاونكما الأول
Yeah, you're right. I'm a little embarrassed.
أجل، أشعر بالإحراج
Husband and wife...
...زوجان
Are you okay, Madam Wife?!
ما الخطب سيدتي الزوجة؟
W... Wife...
...ز-زوجة
Madam Wife!
سيدتي الزوجة؟
W...
...زوجـ
Madam Wife! Madam Wife!
سيدتي الزوجة؟ سيدتي الزوجة؟
W-W...
...زوجـ... زوجـ
Stay with us, Mada–
...تماسكي يا سيدتي الزو
Stop! She'll die!
توقف، ستموت
He called us husband and wife! Oh my!
لقد دعانا بالزوجين
Hey!
أنتِ
What? He suddenly said "Hey" to me!
«ماذا؟ قال لي فجأة «أنتِ
Maybe it's not so bad to have an assertive husband...
امتلاك زوج حازم قد لا تكون فكرة سيئة
No, but it's important to start things right.
لكن يجب أن تكون البدايات جيّدة
I-If you act like my master, I'll kill you, Sanji...
...إ-إن تصرفتَ وكأنّك قوامٌ علي، فسأقتلك يا سانجي
I need you to gather these as fast as you can.
أريد بعض المكونات بسرعة
Non-homogenized milk, sugar beets, bananas, black sesame,
حليب، شمندر السكر، موز، سمسم أسود
roasted soy flour, yogurt. A lot of it.
دقيق صويا محمص، والكثير من اللبن
Yes, sir!
حاضر
...-san !
سان-
Everyone! It's a race against time until the cake is complete!
جميعًا، هذا سباق مع الوقت حتّى تكتمل الكعكة
Chiffon-chan, you bake the giant chiffon cake.
ستعد شيفون-تشان كعكة شيفون الضخمة
Pudding-chan, you handle all the chocolate tempering.
ستتولّى بودينغ-تشان أمر إذابة الشوكولاتة
You have two hours and 40 minutes!
لديكما ساعتان و40 دقيقة
It certainly is a fight against time.
إنّه سباق مع الوقت فعلًا
When we get there, I'll add my secret ingredient!
عندما نصل إلى تلك اللحظة، سأضيف مكوناتي السرية
I'll make you taste true sweetness!
سأجعلكم ترون ماهية الحلوى الحقيقية
T-True sweetness?!
الـ-الحلوى الحقيقية؟
In three hours, we'll load the incomplete cake on a ship and leave Cacao Island.
بعد ثلاث ساعات، سنحمل الكعكة الغير مكتملة على سفينة ونغادر جزيرة الكاكاو
And as we let it cool down, we'll decorate it on the ship.
وبينما ندعها تبرد، سنزيّنها على السفينة
Before we return to the Sunny where Luffy and the others are being chased by Big Mom,
قبل أن نلتقي بلوفي والآخرين المطاردين من قبل بيغ مام وهم على متن سفينة الساني
we'll finish making the greatest cake ever!
سننهي إعداد أروع كعكة على الإطلاق
I see. That sounds efficient.
فهمت، تبدو عملية مُحكمة
But at that fast of a pace?
لكن كيف سننجز ذلك بهذه السرعة؟
No matter how you look at it, that's impossible!
إنّها مستحيلة مهما حاولت
We gotta do it! Do you want Mama to destroy the country?!
يجب أن نفعلها، أتودون أن تدمر ماما الدولة؟
I'm sorry! We'll follow you!
المعذرة، سنبذل ما بوسعنا
All right!
عظيم
Let's start baking!
لنشرع في إعدادها
For those who saved Lola!
من أجل منقذين لولا
For Sanji-san !
من أجل سانجي-سان
I'll make my special extremely-fluffy chiffon cake!
سأعد كعكة شيفون الطرية خاصّتي
I must help Sanji-san and the others get away!
سأساعد سانجي-سان ورفاقه على الهرب
With my very sweet chocolate!
من خلال الشوكولاتة الحلوة خاصّتي
Keep hanging on, guys!
اصمدوا يا رفاق
I'll show them!
...سأريهم
My offensive cooking!
الطبخ على أصوله
Katakuri, it's me.
هذا أنا يا كاتاكوري
You managed to survive, Brother Peros.
لقد نجوت يا أخي بيروس
Yes, barely.
بأعجوبة
That bastard Pedro...
...يا لها من نهاية سخيفة وبائسة
died so pathetically!
انتهى بها بيدرو ذاك
Straw Hat! You were there, weren't you?
قبعة القش، شاهدت ذلك أيضًا، أليس كذلك؟
I suppose he sacrificed his life to try and kill me,
يبدو أنّه أراد قتلي عبر التضحية بحياته التافهة
but I'm very much alive, as you can probably tell.
لكنني ما زلتُ حيًّا أُرزق كما تسمع
So he died for no reason! Right?!
مما يعني أنّ تضحيته ذهبت هباءً، صحيح؟
Why don't you let him kill you already? Lick.
لذا لِمَ لا تستسلم ببساطة-بيرورين؟
What happened to Straw Hat's friends?
ماذا حدث لأتباع قبعة القش؟
Believe it or not,
لقد طاروا بسفينتهم عبر السماء وهربوا من حصارنا
I'm chasing them with Mama now...
إنني أطاردهم حاليًّا برفقة ماما
We're walking on the water.
نحن نسير على الماء
They're tenaciously trying to flee, but we'll catch up to them soon.
إنّهم يحاولون جاهدين الهرب، لكننا سنمسك بهم قريبًا
Amande and the others' fleet will be here soon, too.
سيصل أسطول أماند وبقية الأساطيل قريبًا أيضًا
I see.
فهمت
Brûlée.
بروليه
Ah, Big Brother...
أجل، أخي
How long do you plan on sleeping? Our soldiers can't go anywhere if you keep doing that.
إلى متى تنوين النوم؟ فجنودنا لا يسعهم الذهاب لأيّ مكان أثناء نومك
Okay.
أجل
I thought he might have been able to protect his crew with all of that vigor he's got,
حسبته أنقذ طاقمه عبر قراره الشجاع لكن اتضح أنّ هذا هو حال قبطانهم
Take those soldiers and go set fire or something to Straw Hat's ship.
خذي الجنود وأضرمي النيران في سفينة قبعة القش
Okay!
مفهوم
Big Sister Brûlée!
أختي بروليه
We found a mirror that goes to Straw Hat's ship!
وجدنا مرآة تؤدي إلى سفينة قبعة القش
There must be one or two more!
لا بدّ من وجود واحدة أو أكثر غيرها
All right! Let's shoot flaming arrows at Straw Hat's ship!
عظيم، لنطلق سهامًا نارية في سفينة قبعة القش
I hope they're taken out by Mama while in a frenzy from the fire.
وبينما هم منهمكين بإخماد النيران، ستقضي عليهم ماما
Yikes!
كان ذلك وشيكًا
Give me that mirror!
سلّموني المرآة
Leave them alone!
دعوهم وشأنهم
I thought you wanted to have a one-on-one duel with me, Straw Hat.
ظننتُ أننا نخوض مواجهة فردية يا قبعة القش
That's what you get!
تستحق ذلك
Now, burn down Straw Hat's ship!
والآن، أحرقوا سفينة طاقم قبعة القش برمتها
Roger!
عُلم
Are you ready, Joscar?
هل أنتِ مستعدة يا جوسكر؟
I am, Mascar.
أنا مستعدة يا ماسكر
Now, shoot them!
الآن، أطلقا
Stop!!
توقفوا
No, you stop.
...إيّاك
A mirror!
مرآة
Hey, Nami!
يا نامي
Jinbe, can you hear me?!
جينبي، أتسمعني؟
Somebody, respond!
ليجب أحدٌ ما
Hey! Can you hear me?! Somebody!
أنتم، أيسمعني أحدكم؟
What? Luffy?!
لوفي؟
Nami!
نامي
Luffy, it's me! Are you okay?!
لوفي، هذه أنا، أأنت بخير؟
There are still some mirrors on the ship, right?!
ما زال يوجد بعض المرايا في السفينة، أليس كذلك؟
Maybe in the mens' bedroom or the bathroom?!
ربما في غرفة الرجال أو الحمام؟
It's burning up!
إنّها تحترق
We're gonna shoot, Joscar.
لنطلق النار يا جوسكر
Yes, we are, Mascar.
لنحرقها يا ماسكر
It's burning! It's burning!
إنّها تحترق، تحترق
Luffy?! What'd you say about mirrors?!
لوفي، ماذا بشأن المرايا؟
Break them all! To pieces!
حطمي جميعها إلى أشلاء
Are you out of your mind?! How will you come back if we do that?!
عمّ تتحدث؟ كيف ستعود إذًا؟
I don't know, but I'll be fine!
لا أعرف، لكنني سأجد طريقة
I'll figure something out!
سأتوصل إلى حلٍّ ما
I smell something!
أشمّ رائحة ما
I don't have a nose, though!
رغم أنني لا أملك أنفًا
The bathroom is on fire!
إنّ الغرفة تحترق
What's wrong?!
ما الخطب؟
How is this happening?!
ما الذي حدث؟
Flaming arrows from inside the mirror! Cannon shots from behind!
سهامٌ نارية من المرآة، وطلقات المدافع من خلفنا
One thing after the other! My eyes are spinning!
المصائب تصبُّ علينا، عيناي تدوران
Oh, I don't have eyes that can spin!
رغم أنني لا أملك عينين
In any case, let's put it out, Brook!
على أي حال، لنخمد النيران يا بروك
Now, you guys, keep shooting!
هيّا، لم ينتهِ عملكما بعد
We're gonna keep shooting, Joscar.
سنواصل إطلاق السهام النارية يا جوسكر
Yes, we are, Mascar.
لم ننتهِ بعد يا ماسكر
Stop it, you bastards!
توقفوا أيها الأوغاد
Luffy!
لوفي
Luffy! Are you okay?!
لوفي، أأنت بخير؟
Those of you who'll march onto the ship, follow me!
ليتبعني المكلّفين باقتحام السفينة
Oh, no!
هذا سيئ
Nami! Hurry up and break the mirrors! All of them!
نامي، حطّمي جميع المرايا بسرعة
But...
...ولكن
Our enemies are sending an army your way! I can't stop them by myself!
جيش العدو في طريقه نحوكم، لا يمكنني ردعهم وحدي
Let me focus just on this guy!
لذا دعوني أركز على هذا الشخص فقط
Nami! We have a problem!
نامي، نحن في ورطة
We can't get away!
لا يمكننا الهرب
A high wave!
...موجة عالية
Are you there...?
أتسمعني؟
I'm sorry, Luffy...
...المعذرة يا لوفي
I won't let you get away!
لن أدعكم تهربون
Nami! What's wrong?!
نامي، ما الخطب؟
might be done for...
ربما حانت نهايتنا
Whole Cake Island
جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
At Sea Within the Borders of Totto Land
في البحر داخل حدود توتولاند
Pound Father of Lola and Chiffon
باوند (والد لولا وشيفون)
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Cacao Island
جزيرة الكاكاو
Sweets Factory, Chocolat Town
مصنع الحلوى - بلدة الشوكولاتة
Inside the Factory
داخل المصنع
Whole Cake Island
جزيرة الكعكة الكاملة
Chocolat Town Cacao Island
بلدة الشوكولاتة جزيرة الكاكاو
Mirro-world
عالم المرايا
Mascarpone 34th Son of the Charlotte Family
الابن 34 لعائلة شارلوت ماسكربوني
Joscarpone 29th Daughter of the Charlotte Family
الابنة 29 لعائلة شارلوت جوسكربوني
At Sea, Totto Land
في البحر - توتولاند